reviewsxp.com 2019-07-20

# Reviews XP - Trusted Customer Reviews Portal

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy has been formed keeping those people in mind who are concerned about how we collect, store and use personally identifiable information (PII) of our users. PII are governed by US law on privacy and information security and thus can’t be used arbitrarily by us or anyone for that matter. Do read our privacy policy written in this page carefully to get a clear picture of how we collect, store and disseminate personal information of our users. 

**What kind of information do we really collect from our website visitors and app users?**

We collect your name, email id, phone number and certain other minor details. We collect it when you order something or register on our site. We collect/ask for these info when you order, register or subscribe to one or more services of our site or app. 

**How do we use this information?**

We only use the information collected from you in the following ways:

  * Mainly to improve our services and our platform to give you a more personalized experience
  * Ask you for your feedback on our various services and content from time to time
  * To conduct various contests, promotions and surveys
  * To inform you about our various products and services from time to time

**How do we protect the information we collect from you?**

The information we collect from you (i.e. name, email id, phone numbers etc.) are secured and locked behind a complex security network and can only be accessed by people authorized by us. Only 2-3 people in our company have the authority to access this information. At no point, do we ask for information like credit card details, bank details etc. The network we use to protect information collected by us is encrypted by SSL technology and is thus protected fully from any outside access. 

Also from time to time we run security audits to check if the system is fully functional and if the technology we are using is fully up to date. We also use high-end anti-malware programs to protect ourselves from any kind of virus attack. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes we do, but we do not use them for tracking. You can set your browser setting each time to warn you when a cookie is being sent. That way you can choose to block all cookies. But here’s the catch. If you block cookies, some features on our site may not work properly and you may not get the full experience that we strive to give you. 

**Do we sell or disclose information we collect from you?**

The answer to this question is a resounding NO. Under no circumstance do we sell, disclose or transfer any PIIs we collect from our users to any third party. 

**Do we sell third party products/services on our site?**

Yes we do. From time to time we do sell various third party products and services on our site. If you choose to buy such products or avail of any third party service then you may need to provide your information to those websites/companies. They may have a different privacy policy than our own and we cannot be held responsible if those organization in anyway chooses to misuse those information. 

But rest assured. We DO NOT let any organization with dubious reputation advertise on our website. 

**Advertisement Policy:**

For earning revenue from the site and to keep it running we run adsense advertisement program on our site. Adsense is a product of Google and thus is governed by Google’s policies and we have no say in it. Google also uses DART cookies to run advertisement through adsense on our website and various other sites. These cookies are also governed by Google’s adsense policies and not ours. 

At anytime, users can opt out of advertising programs on our site by changing the settings of Google ad page. Alternatively, they can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on. 

**Contact Us:**

For any query related to our privacy policy or any of our services or any other matter, users can always contact us by filling out the form given in the [Contact Us page](https://www.reviewsxp.com/contact). They can also call us at the numbers given in the said page. 

This privacy policy is subject to change taking place in various legislations and any changes made will be updated here.

Thank you
